libman.com 2004-04-01

# The Libman Company Website Privacy Policy

**_The Libman Company Website Privacy Policy_ **

Effective 01/01/2000 

**Privacy Policy Table Of Contents** :  
Our Commitment To Privacy  
The Information We Collect  
How We Use Information  
Our Commitment To Data Security  
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy  
How To Access Or Correct Your Information  
Opting Out of Promotional Information  
How To Contact Us

**OurCommitment To Privacy **   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**The Information WeCollect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on The Libman Company website. On some pages, you can make requests, submit cleaning tips and comments, enter contests and register to receive information. 

The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, address, email address, phone number, gender, and age.                            

**The Way We UseInformation: **   
We use the information you provide about yourself when you request information only to fulfill that request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to fulfill that request. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive.

Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to submit a cleaning tip or play our trivia game.  If you register you may receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non‑identifying and aggregate information for internal marketing and promotional purposes.  In addition, non‑identifying and aggregate information is used to better design The Libman Company website and to share with our business associates.  For example, we may tell a business associate that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

**Our Commitment To DataSecurity**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures which we deem appropriate to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment ToChildren's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access OrCorrect Your Information**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us at the address below.  We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Opting Out ofPromotional Information**  
We intend to offer visitors to our website only opportunities that will interest them, and we believe they will welcome the information they receive as a result of visiting The Libman Company website.  We may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you.  However, we respect the preference of some of our website’s visitors to limit their Email, mail and telephone calls.  If you would prefer not to receive promotional information as a result of using The Libman Company website, we will do our best to remove your name from our marketing programs.  We will act promptly to honor your request. 

**How ToContact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, our mailing address is _Libman Company, 220 North Sheldon Street, Arcola, IL   61910._  In addition, we can be reached by phone at _(217) 268-4200_ , by fax at _(217) 268-4168_ or send us an email at [info@mamalibman.com](mailto:info@mamalibman.com).
